One question: How can you be sure
it won't blow up?
(Leonard:)-The laser?
-The moon.
(Sheldon:)See, now this is a man for Penny.
(Leonard:)-That's a great question, Zack.
-No, it's not.
-Sheldon, play nice.
-It's not a great question.
(Sheldon:)How could somebody possibly think
we're going to blow up the moon?
(Leonard:)That's a great question.
(Leonard:)Don't worry about the moon.
We set our laser to stun.
(Zack:)Smart.
We'll see the beam when it leaves. It won't
be strong enough when it comes back...
(Leonard:)-...to be seen by the naked eye.
-Naked. Heh, heh, heh.
Right, funny.
So that device there
will measure the photons that return...
...and show it to us on this computer.
Raj, get them some glasses.
(Zack:)Cool, it's gonna be in 3-D?